(FUNKY HIP HOP MUSIC)
♪ GO, GO, GO, GO, GO, GO ♪
♪ GO, SHORTY, IT'S
YOUR BIRTHDAY ♪
♪ WE GON' PARTY LIKE
IT'S YOUR BIRTHDAY ♪
♪ WE GON' SIP BACARDI
LIKE IT'S YOUR BIRTHDAY ♪
♪ AND YOU KNOW WE DON'T GIVE
A IT'S NOT YOUR BIRTHDAY ♪
♪ YOU CAN FIND ME IN THE
CLUB, BOTTLE FULL OF BUB ♪
♪ MAMA, I GOT WHAT YOU NEED,
IF YOU NEED TO FEEL THE BUZZ ♪
♪ I'M INTO HAVIN' SEX, I
AIN'T INTO MAKIN' LOVE ♪
♪ SO COME GIVE ME A HUG, IF
YOU INTO GETTING RUBBED ♪
♪ YOU CAN FIND ME IN THE
CLUB, BOTTLE FULL OF BUB ♪
♪ MAMA, I GOT WHAT YOU NEED,
IF YOU NEED TO FEEL THE BUZZ ♪
♪ I'M INTO HAVIN' SEX, I
AIN'T INTO MAKIN' LOVE ♪
♪ SO COME GIVE ME A HUG, IF
YOU INTO GETTING RUBBED ♪
♪ WHEN I PULL OUT UP FRONT,
YOU SEE THE BENZ ON DUBS ♪
♪ WHEN I ROLL 20 DEEP, IT'S
ALWAYS DRAMA IN THE CLUB ♪
♪ NOW THAT I ROLL WITH DRE
EVERYBODY SHOW ME LOVE ♪
♪ WHEN YOU SELL LIKE EMINEM,
YOU GET PLENTY OF GROUPIE LOVE ♪
♪ LOOK HOMIE, AIN'T NOTHIN'
CHANGED: PROS DOWN, G'S UP ♪
♪ I SEE XZIBIT IN
THE CUT, HEY MAN ♪
♪ WATCH HOW I MOVE,
YOU'LL MISTAKE ME FOR
A PLAYER OR PIMP ♪
♪ BEEN HIT WITH A FEW BUT
I DON'T WALK WITH A LIMP ♪
♪ IN THE HOOD, IN L.A.,
THEY SAYIN', 50, YOU HOT ♪
♪ THEY LIKE ME, I WANT 'EM TO
LOVE ME LIKE THEY LOVE 'PAC ♪
♪ BUT HOLLA IN NEW
YORK, FO' SHO' ♪
♪ THEY'LL TELL YOU I'M LOCO ♪
♪ AND THE PLAN IS TO PUT THE
RAP GAME IN A CHOKEHOLD ♪
♪ I'M FULLY FOCUSED, MAN,
MY MONEY ON MY MIND ♪
♪ GOT A MIL' OUT THE DEAL
AND I'M STILL ON THE GRIND ♪
♪ NOW SHORTY SAID SHE FEELIN'
MY STYLE, SHE FEELIN' MY FLOW ♪
♪ HER GIRLFRIEND WITH HER,
THEY BI AND THEY READY TO GO ♪
♪ YOU CAN FIND ME IN THE
CLUB, BOTTLE FULL OF BUB ♪
♪ MAMA, I GOT WHAT YOU NEED,
IF YOU NEED TO FEEL THE BUZZ ♪
♪ I'M INTO HAVIN' SEX, I
AIN'T INTO MAKIN' LOVE ♪
♪ SO COME GIVE ME A HUG IF
YOU INTO GETTIN' RUBBED ♪
♪ YOU CAN FIND ME IN THE
CLUB, BOTTLE FULL OF BUB ♪
♪ MAMA, I GOT WHAT YOU NEED,
IF YOU NEED TO FEEL THE BUZZ ♪
♪ I'M INTO HAVIN' SEX, I
AIN'T INTO MAKIN' LOVE ♪
♪ SO COME GIVE ME A HUG IF
YOU INTO GETTIN' RUBBED ♪
♪ MY FLOW, MY SHOW,
BROUGHT ME THE DOUGH ♪
♪ THAT BOUGHT ME ALL
MY FANCY THINGS ♪
♪ MY CRIB, MY CARS, MY
CLOTHES, MY JEWELS ♪
♪ LOOK, HOMIE, I DONE CAME
UP AND I AIN'T CHANGED ♪
♪ AND YOU SHOULD LOVE IT
WAY MORE THAN YOU HATE IT
OH, YOU MAD ♪
♪ I THOUGHT THAT YOU'D
BE HAPPY I MADE IT ♪
♪ I'M THAT CAT BY THE BAR
TOASTIN' TO THE GOOD LIFE ♪
♪ MOVED OUT THE HOOD, NOW YOU
TRYIN' TO PULL ME BACK, RIGHT ♪
♪ WHEN MY JOINT GET TO
PUMPIN' IN THE CLUB, IT'S ON ♪
♪ I WINK MY EYE AT YO' CHICK,
IF SHE SMILES, SHE GONE ♪
♪ IF THE ROOF ON FIRE,
MAN, JUST LET IT BURN ♪
♪ THEY TALKIN' ABOUT MONEY,
HOMIE, I AIN'T CONCERNED ♪
♪ I'MA TELL YOU
WHAT BANKS TOLD ME ♪
♪ CUZ, GO 'HEAD,
SWITCH THE STYLE UP ♪
♪ AND IF THEY HATE,
THEN LET 'EM HATE ♪
♪ AND WATCH THE MONEY PILE UP ♪
♪ OR WE CAN GO UPSIDE YOUR
HEAD WITH A BOTTLE OF BUB ♪
♪ COME ON, THEY
KNOW WHERE WE BE ♪
♪ YOU CAN FIND ME IN THE
CLUB, BOTTLE FULL OF BUB ♪
♪ MAMA, I GOT WHAT YOU NEED,
IF YOU NEED TO FEEL THE BUZZ ♪
♪ I'M INTO HAVIN' SEX, I
AIN'T INTO MAKIN' LOVE ♪
♪ SO COME GIVE ME A HUG IF
YOU INTO GETTIN' RUBBED ♪
♪ YOU CAN FIND ME IN THE
CLUB, BOTTLE FULL OF BUB ♪
♪ MAMA, I GOT WHAT YOU NEED,
IF YOU NEED TO FEEL THE BUZZ ♪
♪ I'M INTO HAVIN' SEX, I
AIN'T INTO MAKIN' LOVE ♪
♪ SO COME GIVE ME A HUG IF
YOU INTO GETTIN' RUBBED ♪
DON'T TRY TO ACT LIKE YOU
DON'T KNOW WHERE WE BE NEITHER.
WE IN THE CLUB ALL THE
TIME, SO POP, POP OFF.
SHADY/AFTERMATH. (LAUGHS)
(FUNKY HIP HOP MUSIC)